[Music]
actually in life we got to expect uh
that things might happen anytime to us
so we don't actually buy policy when we
are in need of it so actually we should
buy when during when we are healthy so
most importantly right we got to get
ourself protected so we find that is a
needs to actually get ourself uh covered
for the critical unes and and also the
early critical unes especially as a
income earner in a family any illnesses
strike us right yeah we will know that
we are being covered so that is the best
way to protect our
family initially we put a l s of money
in
today then it's less than a month when I
opened up a letter from manual life I
saw a chck I was I got a shot how come I
got a chair of few hundred you see then
I I called my financial advisor I asked
her what is a chat about and she told me
it's the dividend that I get from the
investment so after when we earn from
the dividend which actually spend for
our housing expenses our lifestyle for
the kids and even can pay our for our
insurance premium uh through a series of
investment we have with manual life we
actually uh for a few years right we
actually earn a certain amounts
of the interest soal the profits so he
enable us to clear our housing loans
it's fully paid so we don't have to pay
a single hand and our financial burden
yeah so it w touch our retirement money
you don't start planning at young age
you won't have money you won you will
have to struggle Until the End better to
plan early and to enjoy it rather than
comes to the day you work very hard but
you don't get to enjoy it then that
would be a way if nothing goes wrong we
can maybe retire in another 20 years oh
10 years something like that
yeah manual life Retirement Solutions
secure today secure tomorrow
tomorrow visit our website to find out
more